# **Mochammad Ichsan**

Jalan Kebon Anggrek, Cipete, Cilandak, 12410, Jakarta Selatan, Indonesia

+62 81291254795 

ichsanmochammad@gmail.com

https://ichsan1710.github.io/personal-portfolio 

ichsan1710

#### **About Me**

Dedicated professional with over six years of experience in the hospitality industry. My journey has now led me to the exciting world of technology, where I am actively pursuing a career as a software developer. My background in hospitality has instilled in me adaptability and problem-solving skills. These skills have seamlessly translated into the technology sector, where I am eager to make a positive impact.

# Languages

- Indonesian (Native)
- English (Fluent)
- German A2.1 (Basic)

### **Technical Skills**

- JavaScript, TypeScript
- Node.js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, PostgreSQL
- o React.js, Three.js, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, Redux, React Native

#### **Education**

Purwadhika Digital Technology Certificate in Bootcamp JC Full Stack Web Development	2023
Swiss German University Bachelor of Economics, Major in International Business	2016

# **Professional Experience**

Mitra POS Lion Parcel Owner	Feb 2022 - Present
Fairmont Jakarta Front Office Supervisor	Jan 2020 - Dec 2021
Fairmont Jakarta Front Desk Agent	Feb 2017 - Jan 2020
Fairmont Jakarta Royal Service Agent	Sep 2016 - Feb 2017
Ayana Resort & Spa Bali Front Desk Agent	Sep 2014 - Sep 2015

Rimba Jimbaran Bali

Daily Worker Guest Service Jul 2014 - Aug 2014

**Kunsportal Century Germany** 

Intern Marketing Apr 2013 - Aug 2013

Weatherford Indonesia

Intern Administration Sep 2011 - Jan 2012

#### **Achievements**

O Top Upseller: Dec 2014, Jan 2015, Aug 2018, Feb 2019, Apr 2020

- o Top Enrollment: Jan 2019, Feb 2019, Mar 2019, Jun 2019, Jul 2019, Aug 2019
- O Perfect Scores LQA Audit Q2 2019
- Employee of the month Fairmont Jakarta Oct 2019